Previously on "Desperate Housewives"
在此前的“欲乱绝情妻”中...
Susan took dating tips from her 12-year-old daughter.
Susan从她12岁的女儿那儿 学到一些约会的小窍门
If you want to date him, you're going to have to ask him out.
如果你想和他约会，你就该约他出来
I keep hoping he'll ask me out.
我一直希望他能来邀请我
How's that going?
结果怎样?
Bree accidentally poisoned her husband.
Bree不小心毒到了她丈夫
I can't believe you tried to kill me.
我真不敢相信你想杀了我
Yes, well, I feel badly about that.
是啊, 我非常抱歉
Lynette indulged in creative parenting.
Lynette沉湎于启发式家长养育
Any of you acts up, I will call Santa, and I will tell him you want socks for Christmas.
你们中任何一个再调皮的话 我就告诉圣诞老人你们不想要圣诞礼物了
I really hate the way you talk to me.
我真讨厌你对我说话的方式
I really hate that I spent $15,000 on your diamond necklace.
我真痛心花了15000元在你的砖石项链上
While Gabrielle indulged in the company of her gardener.
当Gabrielle沉湎于她园丁的陪伴
Hi, honey. You're home early.
嗨, 亲爱的. 你回来真早
And everybody is wondering...
每个人都在想...
Mary Alice, what did you do?
Mary Alice, 你到底干了些什么?
Why their best friend just killed herself.
为什么他们最好的朋友会自杀
How much do we really want to know about our neighbors?
我们真正想了解我们邻居多少呢?
Everyone has a little dirty laundry.
每个人都有一些不可告人之事
After I died,
在我死后
I began to surrender the parts of myself that were no longer necessary.
我呈交出自己不再需要的部分
My desires, beliefs, ambitions, doubts
我的欲望, 信仰, 野心, 疑虑
-
every trace of my humanity was discarded.
人性中的每一抹痕迹都被丢弃
I discovered when moving through eternity,
在穿越来生的时候, 我发现
it helps to travel lightly.
那使我能轻装上路
In fact, I held on to only one thing
事实上, 我只保留了一样东西
my memory.
我的记忆
It's astonishing to look back on the world I left behind
回头看自己身后的世界真是令人吃惊
I remember it all --
我记得所有事情
every single detail.
每一个细节
Like my friend Bree Van De Kamp.
就像我的朋友Bree Van De Kamp
I remember the easy confidence of her smile,
我记得她那悠闲镇定的微笑
the gentle elegance of her hands,
她那举止优雅的双手
the refined warmth of her voice.
她那优雅温和的声音
But what I remember most about Bree...
但Bree给我印象最深刻的是...
Rex, wasn't that lovely
Rex, 那真是可爱, 不是吗
-
was the look of fear in her eyes.
她眼中的恐惧
Bree had started to realize her world was unraveling,
Bree已经开始意识到她的世界正在被瓦解
and for a woman who despised loose ends,
对于一个凡事讲究完美的女人而言
that was unacceptable.
那是无法接受的
Rex. Rex. You need to get up.
Rex, Rex, 你应该起来了
It's not even light out.
天都还没亮
Please hurry.
请快点
If the kids see you sleeping down here, they're going to start asking questions.
如果孩子们看到你睡在这里 他们会开始问一些问题
Let 'em ask. I don't care anymore.
让他们问吧, 我不再介意了
Well, I care.
但是我介意
They don't need to be burden with our marital problems
他们不应当承受我们婚姻问题的压力
while we're working things out, the least we can do is try to keep up appearances.
当我们解决这些事情的时候 我们至少应该试着保持体面
Oh, yeah. Appearances.
哦, 是的, 体面
I keep forgetting about appearances.
我一直忘记要保持体面
Oh, Rex, you look so tired.
哦, Rex, 你看起来很累
I didn't sleep.
我睡不着
This damn thing is so uncomfortable.
这该死的东西让人真不舒服
Well, why don't you move back upstairs and sleep in our bed?
那你为什么不搬回楼上我们的卧室睡？
We're in marriage counseling, Bree.
Bree, 我们在咨询婚姻顾问
I think that would confuse things.
我不想因此而引起误解
It's just
只是
I miss you.
我想你
I know you do.
我知道
Of course, if I don't find out start getting some sleep, pretty soon
当然, 如果我不能想办法睡着, 很快
I'll be forced to move back upstairs out of sure exhaustion.
我就会精疲力竭而被迫搬回楼上
Yes, Bree was afraid of many things,
是的, Bree害怕很多东西
but if there was one thing she wasn't afraid of...
但是如果说有哪样东西她不怕...
It was a challenge.
那就是挑战
Episode 3 : Pretty little picture
第三集: 漂亮的小照片
The day on Wisteria lane began like any other.
在Wisteria lane 又一个如往常般平凡的日子
With a cup of coffee and the moring paper.
在一杯咖啡和一份晨报中开始了
Just give me a second....
等我一下下...
and while Lynette read the business section.
当Lynette读着经济版的时候
and Gabrielle studied the fall collections
Gabrielle计划着秋季收购
and Bree searched for decorating ideas
Bree考虑着室内装潢的点子
Susan scanned the front page and saw something
Susan浏览着头版, 看到一些
that caught her eye
引起她注意的东西
What's about time.
都什么时候了啊
Be nice. I come bearing Snacks.
别那么鸡婆, 我带了些小吃过来
Lynette,  these cards are sticky
Lynette, 这些牌真是粘手
I know. Preston used the three of diamonds to took scoop jam out of the jar.
我知道, Preston拿了三张方块牌 从广口瓶中刮果酱
Gorgeous, thankful we have 49 cards to play with.
太“好”了, 幸亏我们还有49张牌可以玩
- Hello. Sorry I'm late
- 嗨, 不好意思我来晚了
Hey.
嗨
So, Susan and I was just telling the girls, I want to throw a dinner party
对了, Susan和我正在告诉大家 我想举办一个晚宴
- Really?
- 真的?
Yes.
当然
Well how long have we all lived on this street we've never done a big group thing
我们一起在这里住了这么长时间 但从来没有一起做过一件大事
I think it's a great idea
我想那是一个不错的主意
Paul never likes to have people over but the heck with him I'm doing it.
Paul不喜欢家里有很多人 不过管他呢, 我照样要办
So when is this shindig?
什么时候办呢?
How  about a month from tonight?
一个月后如何?
That would be the 16th. Good for everyone?
那就是16号. 大家到时候都有空吗?
Works for me. Should we all make something?
我没问题. 我们都该准备些什么?
Oh, no. This is my party.
哦, 不, 这次我来准备
I've been wanting to have everyone over for years.
我一直期盼这么一个邀请大家过来的机会
I'm so happy we're finally doing this.
我真高兴最终能实现了
It's gonna be so much fun.
那将会很棒
Hey.
嗨
I know. Her dinner.
我知道, 她的晚宴
How could we have all forgotten about this?
我们怎么能忘记了这事呢?
We didn't exactly forget, it's just usually when the hostess dies the party's off.
我们没有忘记 只是随着女主人的去世, 晚宴也取消了
Lynette
I'm not being flip. I'm just pointing out a reality.
不是我轻率无礼, 只是事实如此
Mary Alice was so excited about it. It's so sad.
Mary Alice曾对这次晚餐那么期待 真令人伤心
I  think we should go through with it.
我想我们继续做下去
Really? Wouldn't that be in poor taste?
你说真的? 那会不会很低俗啊?
No. It's sort of a way to honor Mary Alice. It was so important to her
不会, 那可以算是我们对Mary Alice的追思 这件事曾经对她有那么重要的意义
We could all use a fun night.
我们可以有一个愉快的夜晚
Well, good, because I have some new flour that I have been just dying to show off.
嗯, 很好, 我正好有些新面粉 一直没机会展示呢
Lynette?
- I'm in.
- 算我一个
I'll make braised lamb shanks.
我做炖小羊腿
I'm still in.
也算我一个
So how many I will be cooking for?
那么会有多少人参加呢?
Seven. Three couples and Susan. Does that sound right?
七个, 三对夫妻, 还有Susan, 没问题吧?
No,  it sounds very, very wrong.
不, 听起来有很大很大的问题
- Oh
- 哦?
Is there somebody you'd like to invite?
你还想邀请谁吗?
I have an idea.
我有个主意
A dinner party.
一次晚宴
Honey, I may be working late.
亲爱的, 可能我要工作到很晚
The Dillman proposal's a complete mess.
Dillman的建议真是乱糟糟的一片
No, no, you promised to be home every night this week.
不, 不, 你答应这周每晚在家的
This is business.
这是做生意
says the prince as he rides off into the sunset.
王子这样说道, 策马远去没入夕阳之中
Boy the movies ever get the wrong.
电影里说的真是对啊
You know what your problem is?
你知道你的问题是什么吗?
You're very tense.
你太紧张了
You should go to a spa or go shopping.
你应该去做个SPA或者去购物
Find a way to relax.
想个办法放松自己
Hello?
喂?
Where are you?
你在哪里?
Algebra.
上代数课
You free at 4:00?
你4点有空吗?
I'm not sure. I got track after school.
我不确定, 我下课后要参加径赛
Well, get here as fast as you can.
好吧, 那尽快赶来这里
My husband says I need to relax.
我丈夫说我需要放松
You, uh, want me to keep my gym clothes on like last time?
你, 嗯, 要我像上次那样穿着运动服吗?
If you would, please.
如果可以的话, 好啊
A dinner party?
一次晚宴?
Yeah, it'll be fun.
是啊, 那会很有意思的
Bree's cooking, everyone's coming.
Bree掌勺, 大家都会来
You know what? I haven't even had a chance to unpack yet, honey.
你知道么 我都还没有来得及卸下行李呢, 亲爱的
I just, uh, I just need to chill out for the next few days.
我只是, 嗯, 我只是想静静地过几天
Oh, Tom.
哦, Tom
There'll be liquor and hors d'oeuvres and grownups without children and -- and silverware.
晚餐上会有酒, 有小点心 不带孩子来的大人们, 还有银器
Remember silverware?
记得银器吗?
Honey, can you take this in for me?
亲爱的, 可以帮我把这个拿进去吗?
Have you heard anything I just said?
你听到我刚才说的话了吗?
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm just
是的, 对不起 我只是
- I'm wiped out.
- 我实在太累了
Three cities in six days
六天里跑了三个城市
- my head is just pounding. I'm not ready for a dinner party.
- 我的头都大了 我还没准备好参加一次晚宴
I already got a sitter.
我已经找了个看孩子的
Can you cancel her?
还能取消吗？
Please? Look, let's just stay in tomorrow night.
拜托, 我们明晚待在家里吧
We can get a bottle of wine and rent a video,
我们可以买一瓶酒, 还可以租一盘带子
and I just want to hang out with my best gal.
而我我只想和我最爱的女孩儿在一起
That's all.
这就是我所想的
I was looking so forward to a night out.
我是那么期望能有一晚在外度过
I know, sweetie, I'm sorry, but...
我知道, 甜心, 对不起, 但是...
I'm beat.
我太累了
I mean, do you remember what it was like to work a 60-hour week?
你还记得一周工作60小时的日子吗?
A dinner party?
一次晚宴?
Do I have to go?
我一定要去吗?
Well, given that we're hosting it, I'd say so.
既然是我们主办, 我会说是的
By the way, you won't be drinking at this party.
顺便提一下, 在晚宴上你不能喝酒
Why is that?
为什么不?
Because when you drink, you get chatty.
因为每次你一喝酒话就开始多
No one needs to know that we're seeing Dr. Goldfine.
我不想别人知道 我们在Goldfine医生那儿咨询
You know, if you spent half as much time working on our problems as you do covering them
如果你能将花在掩盖问题上时间的一半 用来处理这些问题
-
not a drop.
一滴都不准喝
You know, this
这
- this is ridiculous.
这真是荒谬
And this whole thing about us taking tennis lessons?
而我们上网球课这事?
Well,  the nurses at your office may start wondering why you're disappearing three times a week.
你手下的护士可能已经开始猜测 为什么你一周会有三次都不在
Tennis lessons are a plausible alibi.
上网球课这借口看上去不错
All right so, these tennis lessons we're taking
好吧, 我们所上的网球课里
-
how are we doing?
我们的进度如何?
My backhand's improving immensely, but you're still having problems with your serve.
我的反手击球提高很快 但你发球还存在很大问题
Of course.
当然
A dinner party?
一次晚宴?
It's tomorrow night, so if you could just keep Julie an extra day.
在明天晚上, 所以你能不能多带Julie一天
Fine, but that's all. Brandi and I leave sunday for a week up at the cabin.
好吧, 但就一天 Brandi和我周日要离开去林间小屋呆一周
What cabin?
什么林间小屋?
Brandi wanted some place where we could get away.
Brandi想找一个远离喧嚣的地方
Escrow just closed yesterday.
Escrow昨天刚关门
You can afford a cabin, but you can't scrape up child support?
你有钱去住林间小屋 却攒不够孩子的赡养费?
The check is in the mail.
支票已经邮寄了
Oh. No, it's not.
哦, 不, 还没
I found my dental guard. I'm ready.
我找到我的护齿了, 可以走了
Stop fighting.
别吵架了
We are being as nice as we possibly can to one another.
我们互相之间已经尽可能地善待对方了
Like I said, stop fighting.
就像我刚才所说的, 别吵架了
Excuse me, Brandi.
不好意思, Brandi
Do you mind?
你介不介意...
Oh, okay.
哦, 好的
Wait. Susan, you're right there. You can pick it up.
等一下, Susan, 你就在那儿 你可以把它捡起来
I could, but she's the one who threw it.
我可以, 但是东西是她扔的
Come on. Don't be petulant. Just pick up the stupid can.
拜托, 别耍性子了 把那个该死的罐头捡起来吧
No.
没门
I can pick it up.
我来捡吧
Honey, stay out of this.
亲爱的, 你别牵扯进来
Fine.
好吧
This is so typical.
这真是典型的你我关系啊
Oh, I'm sorry. Was that petulant, too?
哦, 对不起, 那也是耍性子?
You know what? You can pick up the damn can yourself.
你知道么, 你可以自己捡起那该死的罐子
Yeah, well, you just go to hell.
是的, 对, 你去死吧
You  want me to pick it up?
你要我把它捡起来吗?
Uh...
嗯...
Mrs. Warmington said she looked for mom's obituary and couldn't find it.
Warmington夫人说她在找妈妈的讣告 但是没找到
Did you put one in?
你在报上登过吗?
I've had other things on my mind, Zack.
Zack, 我在考虑其他的事情
But how could you not do that?
但你怎么能不登讣告呢?
People are going to think we didn't care about her.
人们会认为我们不关心她
I doubt people will give it much thought.
我认为人们不会有很多想法
Don't worry about it.
别担心
You never talk about her.
你从未谈起过她
She hasn't even been dead a month, and it's like you've totally forgotten she ever existed.
她死了还没一个月 你就完全忘了她, 就像根本没她这人一样
It's a little early for this kind of talk.
现在谈论这个太早了点
Maybe when you die,
也许等你死的时候
I won't put in an obituary.
我也不会为你登讣告
That will be your choice to make.
那由你说了算
Assuming you outlive me.
假如你能比我活得更久
Mom, it's no big deal.
妈妈, 那没什么大不了的
Carlos and I are driving in for the baptism.
Carlos和我会赶来参加洗礼
Problem solved.
这样就没问题了
Okay, fine.
好, 不错
You go with aunt Maria, and I will take Nana to church.
你跟着Maria阿姨, 我会带着Nana去教堂的
Uh-huh.
嗯
Okay. I got to go, mom.
好了, 我有事要挂电话了, 妈妈
Yes, right now.
对, 就现在
Okay, uh, you can give me directions later. Bye.
好的, 你晚点再告诉我怎么走吧, 再见
Hi. How was school?
嗨, 在学校过得怎么样?
Got an A-minus on my biology exam.
生物考试得了A-
You did? Mm.
真的?
Well, let's see what you've learned.
很好, 让我们看看你都学了些什么
Who's that?
那是谁?
I don't know.
我不知道
Hey,  you!
嗨!
So did Mike say anything?
Mike说过些什么吗?
No, but, god, you should have seen the look on his face.
没有, 但是, 你真该看看当时他的表情
I'm sure it's not that bad.
我相信不会那么糟糕
I mean, he's coming to the party, right?
我的意思是, 他会来参加晚会的吧?
I left three messages.
我留了三条消息
Oh, he's not going to come. Big surprise.
哦, 他不会来的, 和我想的一样
I did everything but foam at the mouth.
除了没唾沫飞溅外, 我什么难听话都说了
God, I hate when I get that way.
天啊, 我真厌恶自己会那样做
It's like every time I get within 10 feet of Karl, I just become this monster.
好像每次我和Karl走近到10英尺的范围内 我就变得像怪物一样
You know what? It's not going to change until you resolve your issues with that man.
你知道么, 那种情况不会改变 直到你解决了和他的问题
What, you mean forgive him?
什么? 你说要我原谅他?
You know, I've lived with this bitterness so long, I think I'd be lonely without it.
这苦痛已经伴随我太长时间了 没了它的话会让我觉得孤单
Honey, get a pet.
亲爱的, 养个宠物吧
See ya.
再见
- Son of a
- 狗娘
-
it's a business meeting.
那是一次商务会谈
It's a frat party.
是一次兄弟聚会
Regional manager, corporate manager, head of sales.
区域经理, 公司经理, 销售负责
Margarita, cigar, sombrero.
Margarita酒, 雪茄, 宽边帽
Okay.
好吧
Honey, what do you want me to do, sit around the hotel the whole time watching cable?
亲爱的, 你想要我怎么做 在酒店里整天看有线电视?
No.  But when I say,
不, 但当我说
"we've been invited to a party,"
“我们被邀请去参加一个派对”
don't whine about your exhausting 60-hour week.
不要拿一周60小时工作的辛苦作借口
Put on your dancin' shoes and take the mother of your children out for a good time.
穿上一身好衣服 带着你老婆出去度过一段美好时光
Fine. You know what? You're right.
好吧, 你说得对
Let's go to that party.
我们去参加那个晚会
I can't. I already canceled the sitter.
不行了, 我已经取消了那个临时保姆
Okay, well, we'll throw the next one.
好吧, 那下次我们来办
Throw a dinner party?
办一次晚宴?
I don't even have time to wash my face.
我甚至都没时间洗脸
No, you know what?
不, 你知道我怎么想吗?
I'm going to go to this one.
我去参加这次的
You can stay home and babysit the kids.
你可以呆在家里照顾孩子们
Fine.
好的
I can handle that.
我能办到
Thank you.
谢谢
Gabrielle spent her morning searching for the mysterious little girl.
Gabrielle花了一个早上 寻找那神秘的小女孩
Sadly for her, the mystery was solved a bit too quickly.
不幸的是, 谜团过早得被揭开了
Hey.
嗨
What's going on?
你们在聊什么?
Have you met Ashley?
你见过Ashley吗?
Found it!
我找到它了!
Babe, this is Sheila Bukowski, our new neighbor. They just moved into the Miller's old house.
宝贝儿, 这位是Sheila Bukowski 我们的邻居, 他们刚搬进Miller的老房子
My daughter left her ball in your yard. I'm so sorry.
我女儿把球扔进你们院子了, 真对不起
Oh, oh, no
哦, 哦, 不
- no problem.
- 没关系
Nice to meet you, Ashley.
很高兴见到你, Ashley
She's shy. She doesn't say much.
她很害羞, 不怎么说话
Yeah, but I can see her little mind working away.
是啊, 不过我看得出来她脑子里很活跃
Nice meeting you.
很高兴见到你
Come on, Ashley.
来吧, Ashley
Private sessions?
单独谈话?
I don't understand. Why do we need private sessions?
我不明白, 我们干嘛要进行单独谈话?
Private sessions allow us to work on the personal issues of both partners.
单独谈话使能我们解决双方各自的私人问题
Oh, well, I don't have any personal issues.
哦, 我没有任何私人问题
My only issue is that my husband wants to leave me, and how can I work on that if he's not in the room?
我唯一的问题是我丈夫要离开我 如果他不在场, 我怎么解决它呢?
There are things I need to discuss with Dr. Goldfine, and I can't have you there.
我要和Goldfine医生说一些事 而我不希望你在场
Why?
为什么不?
I'm your wife. You can say anything in front of me.
我是你的妻子 你可以在我面前说任何事情
All we need is a few more sessions, and I'm sure we can
我们只需要再多几次谈话 我肯定我们能
-
damn it, Bree,
该死, Bree
a few more sessions isn't going to fix us.
再多的谈话也没用
This is bigger than that.
我们的问题不是谈话能解决的
Why don't we do it this way?
要不我们这样吧?
Rex, you can take the first half-hour.
Rex, 你前半小时来
Bree, you can take the second.
Bree, 你后半小时来
Fine.
很好
Oh, and, doctor,
哦, 医生
if  what he's about to discuss has anything to do with adultery, prostitution, or internet pornography,
如果他想谈论有关通奸 卖淫, 或者网络色情资料
I would really appreciate you taking a moral hard line.
我非常希望你能严厉斥责他
Hi, Ashley.
嗨, Ashley
Remember me? We
记得我吗? 我们
- we met earlier.
- 我们早先见过
Wow.
喔
Aren't you the little artist? Ha ha.
你真是个小艺术家啊, 呵呵
What are those
那些是什么
- flamingos?
- 火烈鸟?
No.
不是
Well, they're very pretty.
它们真漂亮
It almost looks like they're kissing.
看起来它们好像在亲吻
Funny thing about kissing
亲吻的有趣之处在于
-
it's not just for husbands and wives.
那不仅限于丈夫和妻子
Sometimes we kiss our mom or our grandpa.
有些时候我们会亲吻妈妈或者祖父
Sometimes we even kiss our dog. Ha ha.
有时候我们甚至会亲吻我们的狗, 呵呵
Sometimes we even kiss people who are just our friends,
有时候我们甚至亲吻我们的朋友
kind of like a high-five on the lips. Right? Ha ha.
就像是用嘴唇来个 high-five(举手击掌致意), 对吧? 呵呵
Uh... hey, Ash,
嗯...嗨, Ash
I was at the mall, and I saw this.
我在商场里看到这个
I thought you might like it.
我想你可能喜欢她
She's hawaiian.
她是夏威夷人
Her name is princess kahalua,
名字是Kahalua公主
and I think it means "little waterfall," or "big pond" or something.
我想那意思是“小瀑布” 或者“大池塘”或者其他什么
Okay.
好吧
So we're good, right?
那么我们扯平了, 对吧?
Okay.
好吧
Well, you enjoy your new little friend,
很好, 和你的新伙伴玩得开心点
and if there's anything else you need, you just let me know.
如果你还想要什么, 告诉我好了
What I'd really like
我真正想要的是
is a bike.
一辆自行车
Where did you find that?
你在哪儿找到它的?
She used this to kill herself.
她是用这个自杀的
Why would you keep it?
你为什么留着它?
Why?
为什么?
Because I thought we might need it someday.
因为我想也许我们有一天会用得着
For what?
用来干嘛?
Protection.
自卫
I want to talk about mom.
我想谈谈妈妈的事
You need to take your medication.
你该吃药了
We are going to talk about mom.
我们谈谈妈妈的事
Hello, Zack.
你好, Zack
I hope this isn't a bad time.
希望没有妨碍到你
What can I do for you, Mrs. Van De Kamp?
Van De Kamp夫人 有什么能为你效劳的吗?
Well, I wanted to invite you and your father to a dinner party tomorrow night.
我想邀请你和你的父亲参加明天的晚宴
I'm not sure where he is right now.
我不知道他现在在哪里
Oh. Well, I'm sorry it's such late notice, but, well,
哦, 真抱歉这么晚才通知你, 不过
we weren't sure that you and your father were ready for any kind of social engagement yet,
我们都不敢肯定你和你的父亲 是否有心情参加社交活动了
but, we're sort of throwing it in your mother's honor.
不过, 我们是以纪念你母亲的名义组织的
Really?
真的?
Yes, it's just going to be a casual night with the gang.
是啊, 就是大家在一起轻松一下
We're going to eat and tell fun stories about your mom.
我们会吃点东西 并谈谈你母亲的一些趣事
Zack... are you okay?
Zack... 你没事吧?
Hello, Bree.
嗨, Bree
Oh, hi, Paul. I was just
哦, 嗨, Paul, 我只是
-
I heard.
我听到了
Thank you, but we already have plans for tomorrow.
多谢, 不过我们明天已经有计划了
Oh. That's too bad.
哦, 真可惜啊
Well, I should go.
好了, 我该走了
Thank you, Mrs. Van De Kamp.
谢谢, Van De Kamp夫人
For what, Zack?
为了什么, Zack?
Remembering my mom.
纪念我的母亲
That night, Paul gave his son something to calm his nerves,
那个夜晚, Paul给了他儿子一些东西 安抚他紧张的情绪
and the next day, Gabrielle calmed her own nerves by giving something to her new best friend.
第二天, Gabrielle给了她新的最好朋友 一些东西来缓解自己的紧张情绪
Here you go.
给你
Top of the line, 3-speed, aluminum frame, handlebar ribbons, and a bell,
高规格, 3倍变速, 铝制架 把手上有丝带, 还有一个铃
and you'll notice it's royal blue to match your pretty little eyes.
你会发现这个品蓝色很配你漂亮的小眼睛
My eyes are green.
我的眼睛是绿色的
Yeah, well, you'll be cruising so fast on this, no one will even notice.
是啊, 不过在你骑车疾驰的时候 没有人会注意到的
It's all yours, hon.
是你的了, 亲爱的
Have fun.
玩得开心点
What? What's wrong?
什么? 怎么了?
I don't know how to ride a bike.
我不知道怎么骑自行车
What?
什么?
Well, then, why did you ask for one?
那么, 你为什么要一辆车?
Why can't you show me?
你可以教我啊
Ha ha. well.
呵呵, 好啊
Sure, one of these days.
近期某一天吧
What's wrong with now?
为什么不能是现在?
After her talk with Lynette,
在和Lynette交谈之后
Susan decided to take a look at her old photo album,
Susan决定看一下她的旧相册
and she began to see herself in a whole new light,
她开始用新眼光看她自己
and the picture wasn't flattering.
而那些照片并没能让她开心起来
Yeah, you got Karl. Leave a message.
喂, 我是Karl, 请留言
Hey, Karl, it's me.
嗨, Karl, 是我
I was hoping you'd be there.
我希望你在
Um, listen, we need to talk,
嗯, 听着, 我们需要谈一下
so maybe when you drop Julie off tomorrow,
也许你明天送Julie过来的时候
we could have a moment.
我们可以谈一会儿
It's important.
有重要的事
Give my best to...
替我向Brandi...
Brandi.
问好
Call me.
打电话给我
Susan was proud of herself.
Susan为自己骄傲
She was finally ready to let go of her anger.
她终于能够抛开她的愤怒了
Well...
也许只是...
almost.
几乎能够
The boys will be hungry at 5:30,
孩子们在5点半的时候会开始饿
so put the fish sticks in the toaster oven at 5:00.
所以在5点的时候把鱼棒放进烤箱
For half an hour. Honey.
- 烤30分钟
I know. This is the third time you've told me.
亲爱的, 我明白了, 你已经说了三次了
Well, if the food's late, god help you.
好, 如果食物弄晚了 就只有上帝能帮你了
Beautiful, I don't need a pamphlet.
很好, 我不需要指导手册
It's not brain surgery.
这又不是脑外科手术
They're just kids, for god sake.
看在上帝的份上, 他们只是孩子
Preston, would you come here?
Preston, 过来一下好吗?
Yeah?
好的
Sweetie,
亲爱的
you know our rule about eating cookies, right?
你知道我们吃点心的规矩, 对吧?
Yeah, we can't have them after 5:00 'cause sugar makes us hyper.
是的, 我们必须在5点以后才可以吃 因为糖会使我们亢奋
Yeah, but tonight, anything goes.
是啊, 但是今晚, 没有任何约束
Make sure you share with your brothers.
保证你和你的弟弟一起分享
Thanks, mom.
多谢, 妈妈
Don't look at your feet. Don't look at your feet.
别看着你的脚, 别看着你的脚
Look at the road. Look at the road. Good.
看着路, 看着路, 很好
Ow. Okay.
好的
Find your balance. Find your balance.
保持平衡, 保持平衡
Okay, it's all you. It's all you! You're doing great!
好的, 就这样, 就这样! 干得不错!
Okay, stay to the right. Watch the car.
好的, 保持在右侧, 当心别撞到车
Watch the car! Watch the car!
当心车! 当心车!
Oh, god.
哦, 天啊
Oh! Are you okay?
哦! 你还好吧?
Yeah. Let's go again.
是的, 再来一次吧
Oh, honey, these heels don't have another block in them.
我的高跟鞋后跟坏了(我不能陪你玩了)
What about tomorrow?
明天怎么样?
Well, you won't be around tomorrow, 'cause you have school.
你明天不能在这儿, 你该上学去
I'm homeschooled.
我在家自学
I'm always around.
我一直有空
It was in that moment that Gabrielle realized this ride was far from over.
就在那一刻, Gabrielle意识到 这次的自行车教学远没到尽头
I'm coming!
来了!
Karl, what are you doing here? I asked you to come tomorrow.
Karl, 你在这干什么? 我让你明天来
You said you wanted to talk. It sounded important.
你说你想谈谈, 听上去很重要的样子
Tomorrow. I'm in a towel.
明天! 我全身只裹着条浴巾
We were married 14 years.
我们结婚14年了
I know what's under there. Come on.
我知道那下面有些什么, 说吧
I'm not really ready for this.
我还没准备好
I was going to have a whole speech prepared.
我本来是打算把想说的东西整个准备好的
Brandi and I have plans tomorrow.
Brandi和我明天有计划了
I suggest you wing it.
我建议你还是即兴发挥吧
um, okay.
嗯, 好吧
Here's the thing, Karl
是这样的, Karl
-
I was thinking about what happened in the driveway yesterday,
我在想昨天在车道上发生的事情
and... I-I just don't want to
我
-
我只是不想--
I don't want to live like that.
我不想那样子生活
I don't want to be that kind of person,
我不想做那样的人
and I just thought if the two of us, you know, if we had a nice, calm
而且我想如果我们两个, 你知道 如果我们能有一个愉快, 冷静
-
I need an apology, Karl.
我要你道歉, Karl
A what?
什么?
An apology for the way you ended our marriage.
要你为这样终止我们婚姻而道歉
You never took any responsibility for your behavior.
你对于你的行为从来没有负责过
I don't know what to say, Susan.
我不知道该说什么, Susan
The heart wants what it wants.
一切顺从心意
What does that mean?
什么意思?
I fell in love.
我爱上别人了
While you were married to someone else.
在你已经和其他人结婚的时候
The heart wants what it wants.
一切顺从心意
Yeah, well, my heart wants to hurt you, but I can control myself.
是啊, 我心里想伤害你, 但我能控制自己
I don't want to go back to that ugly place, really,
我我真的不想再回到那种不愉快的境地
and if you do, I suggest that you get some help.
如果你想的话, 我建议你寻求一些帮助
You know what?
你知道么
I don't need an apology.
我不需要一个道歉
I don't need anything from you.
我不想从你那儿得到任何东西
You're humiliating yourself.
你在羞辱你自己
No, you're the one who's been humiliated, Karl.
不, 被羞辱的人是你, Karl
Why don't you see that?
为什么你不明白呢?
You walked out on your family.
你抛下了自己的妻女
People think you're scum, not me,
人们会认为你是渣子, 而不是我
so worry about yourself. I'm okay with me.
所以担心担心你自己吧, 我可很好
I can walk down the street and hold my head high.
我能昂首挺胸地走在街上
As the sun slowly settled on Wisteria lane,
当太阳缓缓地在Wisteria lane落山
an unsettled Susan racked her brain to find a way into her own house.
手足无措的Susan绞尽脑汁 想着回到自己家里的办法
Lying naked in her shrubs,
裸身躺在她家的灌木丛中
it occurred to Susan this could be the most humiliating moment of her life.
Susan心里想道 这可能是她一生中最丢脸的一刻了
Susan?
She was wrong.
她错了
Uh, whatcha doing?
嗯, 你在干什么啊?
Locked myself out...
把自己锁在外面了...
naked.
赤裸地
Oh.
哦
And then I fell.
而且后来我又摔倒了
So how are you?
你现在怎样?
Good, good.
很好, 很好
I just got back.
我刚回来
I've been gone all day, and I got your messages about dinner,
我出去了一整天 刚看到你有关晚餐的留言
and, um, I would love to come if that invite still stands.
嗯, 如果那邀请还有效的话, 我愿意去
It's a date.
那是一次约会
All right. I, um...
好的, 我, 嗯...
assume the dress is casual.
我想我可以随意着装吧
Yeah. It's
是的, 可以
- it's casual.
- 可以随意着装
Thanks for helping me break in.
谢谢你帮我把门打开
Do you think it'll be hard to replace that screen?
你能忘掉刚才的情景吗?
It depends.
看情况吧
If you nail it in yourself, you might want to wear gloves...
如果你把自己“钉”在那儿 你也许会想要戴副手套...
or pants. Pants wouldn't hurt.
或者穿条裤子, 那样不会刺痛
Okay, I know what just happened is funny in theory,
好吧, 我知道那事理论上来说很有趣
but I'm nowhere near ready to laugh about it, so please, no jokes.
但我现在还不想拿它开玩笑 所以拜托, 别开玩笑
Hey, where have you two been?
嗨, 你们两个哪儿去了?
Uh, Susan had a problem finding something to wear.
嗯, Susan找不到东西穿
Oh, is that the kind of thing you meant?
哦, 是这样吧?
Pretty much.
差不多
The kids are bouncing off the walls? Huh.
孩子们在上窜下跳? 嗯
Well, I'm sure you can figure a way to put them to bed, Tom.
很好, 我想你会有办法 让他们上床睡觉的, Tom
I mean, for god sakes, Tom, they're just kids.
我说, 看在上帝份上, Tom 他们只不过是孩子
Hey. Are you okay?
嗨, 你没事吧?
Yes, I went jogging today,
是的, 我我今天去慢跑了
and I think I just pushed myself too hard.
我想我大概有点跑得过度了
Oh, you're probably not wearing the right shoes.
哦, 你可能没有穿对鞋子
Yeah, that thought did cross my mind.
是啊, 我也这么想过
So Gabrielle says that you and Bree are taking lessons three times a week.
Gabrielle说, 你和Bree每周上三次课
Uh-huh.
嗯
I'm actually thinking about playing again. I mean, it's such great exercise.
我在考虑是否重新开始打网球 我是说, 那种运动太棒了
Mm. That it is.
嗯, 是啊
And my drop shot could use a serious tune-up.
我的扣球技术需要好好调整一下
Think you can give me the number of your pro?
能给我你教练的电话吗?
Yeah. I'll, uh, I'll give it to you later.
当然, 我, 我等会儿给你
Well, what club does he work out of?
他在哪个俱乐部工作?
Um...
嗯...
w-we're not really taking tennis lessons, carlos.
我们-我们实际上没去上网球课, Carlos
You're not?
你们没去?
That's a story
那是编出来的
Bree concocted to cover the fact that we're seeing a marriage counselor.
Bree编造了这个来掩盖 我们在咨询婚姻顾问的事实
Bree
- Bree...
he wouldn't stop asking about the tennis pro.
他一直在问有关网球教练的事
Bree and I are in marriage counseling.
Bree和我在咨询婚姻顾问
Everyone knows our secret now.
现在每个人都知道我们的秘密了
Did the sky fall?
天塌下来了吗?
Has your life come crashing down?
你的生活变得一团糟了吗?
If everybody would please take your seats,
请大家各就各位
dinner is served.
开始上菜了
With the winds from the northwest at 4 miles per hour, it's currently 55 degrees.
伴随着时速4英里的西北风 它目前已经55度了
Now we go to rich... live on the scene in westbrook.
我们现在把镜头切换给Rich 他在Westbrook为我们现场报道
A grisly discovery was made today in westbrook when a chest was found in rockwater lake,
今天在Westbrook有一个可怕的发现 一只箱子在Rockwater湖
discovered by a local area businessman and his grandson while they were fishing.
被一个当地生意人和他的孙子 在钓鱼的时候发现
Investigators recovered a wooden chest containing what appears to be human remains.
调查员发现一个木箱子 里面装着看上去像是人类骸骨的东西
Now, a police spokesman says the body was
警方一名发言人表示这尸体是
-
Okay, I got to break the ice here.
好吧, 我想我该打破这里的沉默
So you're in counseling. Big deal.
你们在咨询婚姻顾问, 没什么大不了的
You want humiliation? I'll give you humiliation.
你们知道什么是羞耻吗? 我告诉你什么是羞耻
I locked myself out of my house stark naked and got caught by Mike.
我把我自己完全赤裸地锁在门外 而且正好被Mike发现
Oh, my god. When did this happen?
哦, 天啊, 什么时候的事情?
Today, right before the party.
今天, 就在聚会之前
What can I say? Right place, right time.
我能说什么呢? 正巧碰到了
I think I can top that. Try getting thrown out of disneyland for lewd behavior.
我想我最离谱了 因为下流行为被赶出迪斯尼乐园
What? When was this?
什么? 这又是什么时候的事啊?
When Tom and I were first married, things got a little out of hand on Mr. Toad's wild ride.
Tom和我刚结婚的时候, 在Toad先生的 Wild Ride上有些事情变得无法控制
You're kidding.
你在开玩笑吧
No. We got perp walked down main street, USA.
当然没有, 我们像罪犯一样 走在美国主街上
Well, since we're doing true confessions,
既然我们在做真诚忏悔
Carlos and I once broke a waterbed in Cancoon.
Carlos和我在Cancoon打破了一张水床
How'd you manage that?
你们怎么做到的?
Well, he used to have a thing for spiked heels.
他以前对高跟鞋上的后跟有癖好
I'd just like to make it clear
我只想说清楚
- she was wearing them.
- 她穿着它们
Rex cries after he ejaculates.
Rex在射精后会哭
You think we left too early?
你觉得我们离开得太早了?
I was thinking we left too late.
我想我们离开得太晚了
So is, uh, Rex gone for good?
那么, Rex是要永久离家了吗?
I don't know.
我不知道
God, I hope not.
天啊, 我不希望这样
I mean, they've always been wound a little tight, but I've never seen them like that.
他们的关系总是有点紧张 但我从来没见过他们那样
Then again, who am I to judge?
不过话说回来, 我哪有资格评论人家呢?
You mean people who live in glass houses shouldn't throw soda cans?
你的意思是处于类似境地的你 不应当评论他人?
Okay, you have got to know that I only get that angry around Karl.
你要知道我只是对Karl很恼火
He just treated me so badly at the end.
他在最后那段时间对我太差了
I haven't been able to get past it.
我无法摆脱那种情绪
Well, maybe he did you a big favor.
也许他帮了你一个大忙
What do you mean?
什么意思?
Let's look at Karl as a starter marriage
让我们把Karl看作是婚姻的起步阶段
- you know, boot camp.
- 就像, 新兵训练营
Preparing you for something better next time.
使你对下一次婚姻有更好的准备
Listen, Mike...
Mike...
about the whole seeing me naked thing, I...
关于看到我裸体的事情, 我...
I don't
我不
- I just want to thank you for being such A... perfect gentleman.
- 我只是想谢谢你表现得 如此绅士
Oh, I wasn't a perfect gentleman. I might have snuck a peek.
哦, 我不是什么完美的绅士 我可能鬼鬼祟祟地偷看了
Good night.
晚安
And, um, for what it's worth...
嗯, 我所看到的应当得到一个...
Wow.
喔
Hi.
嗨
How was your night?
今晚过得如何?
We are raising little terrorists. You know that, don't you?
我们养了一群小恐怖分子 你知道的, 对吧?
Oh. You didn't have a good time?
哦, 你过得不开心?
Okay, you know what? Drop the act.
好啦, 我说你别装了!
I know you gave them cookies.
我知道你给了他们饼干
Oh. Who cracked, anyway?
哦, 不管怎样, 是谁搞砸了呢?
Porter.
Porter
Oh.
哦
So how was your, uh, dinner party?
你的, 嗯, 晚宴怎么样?
Well, there was dinner, but it wasn't much of a party.
有一顿晚餐, 不过不那么开心
Uh-oh. What happened?
啊哦, 怎么了?
I don't know.
我不知道
Rex announced that he and Bree are in counseling.
Rex告诉大家, 他和Bree在咨询婚姻顾问
She retaliated with this whole revelation which I won't even go into now,
而她则以揭Rex的老底为报复 我现在都不想提起她所说的事
and the bottom line is he stormed out.
结果他大发雷霆地离开了
Clearly, there's trouble in paradise.
看起来, 在天堂里也会有麻烦
Honestly, I'm not that surprised.
老实说, 我并不觉得吃惊
Why not?
为什么?
I don't know. I just never got the idea that they were really happy.
不知道, 我只是从来没觉得 他们真的很幸福
Are we happy?
我们幸福吗?
Man, oh, man.
天啊, 哦, 天啊
I keep seeing that look on Rex's face,
我看到Rex脸上一直挂着那种表情
and then him taking off like that.
然后他就像那样离开
Some night.
某个晚上
Then again, I would probably cry, too, if I had to have sex with that woman.
如果我和那个女人发生性关系 我很可能也会哭
I mean, you watch a man get torn down like that,
我是说, 你看到一个男人像那样被羞辱
it makes you wonder why he let her get away with it.
你会想为什么他就这样放过了她
Believe me, if a woman ever humiliated me like that in public,
相信我, 如果一个女人像那样 在公共场合羞辱我
hm--it would only happen once.
嗯--那她就玩完了
So, uh, where are you going?
你去哪里?
I'll be staying at the motor lodge.
我会呆在汽车旅馆
The hotel by the interstate has better rates, and it's closer to your work.
洲际饭店价格更合适 那也靠近你的工作的地方
Fine.
很好
I'm packing your swimsuit.
我正在打包你的泳衣
There's a pool there, and I know how swimming relaxes you.
那里有个游泳池 我知道游泳让你觉得很放松
When our kids ask where I am, what are you going to say?
当我们的孩子问我在哪里, 你会怎么说?
Um...
嗯...
I could tell them that you went to tennis camp.
我会告诉他们你去参加网球集训营了
That was a joke.
我在开玩笑
Yeah. I got it.
是的, 我知道
Ah. There.
哈, 好了
Obviously, if you've forgotten anything, you can, um, come right back and get it.
当然, 如果你忘记了什么东西 你可以马上回来拿
Well, I'll call you.
好, 我会打电话给你的
Rex.
Rex
In college, when we first started dating,
大学里, 当我们刚开始约会的时候
people were so jealous of us.
人们都在嫉妒我们
We were the golden couple.
我们是极好的一对
Everybody knew we were going to have this wonderful life.
人人都知道我们会有这样美好的生活
Why is this happening?
现在为什么会变成这样?
Because you can't even let me pack my own suitcase.
因为你甚至都不让我打包自己的衣箱
All right, see ya. Have fun.
好吧, 再见, 开心点
Hey.
嗨
Where are you going?
你去哪儿?
Just a sec.
等一下
Mom?
妈妈?
Don't worry. I'm not packing heat.
别担心, 我不会火上浇油的
Hey, Brandi, would you scoot a little?
嗨, Brandi, 你能稍微挪一下吗?
Just scoot. Thank you.
稍微挪一下, 多谢
Hi.
嗨
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
I'll be quick.
我很快就好
Brandi, I'm sorry for the way I treated you.
Brandi, 对不起我以前那样待你
It was uncalled for and childish, and it won't happen again.
那都是些不必要的孩子气 再也不会发生了
I have built up a lot of anger towards you, both of you,
我以前一直对你们两个很生气
and I realize now that I just can't carry that around anymore,
现在我意识到我不能再在愤怒中过日子了
so apology or no apology,
所以不管你道不道歉
I'm moving on.
我已经重新振作起来了
Mrs. Mayer?
Mayer夫人?
Brandi.
Brandi
Brandi, get in the car.
Brandi, 上车来
Mrs. Mayer.
Mayer夫人
Please, call me Susan.
请叫我Susan
I just wanted you to know
我只想让你知道
what happened between me and Karl, things got out of hand
我和Karl之间发生的事情有点失去控制
because I thought your marriage was over.
因为我以为你们的婚姻已经结束了
Anyway, I just wanted you to know I'm sorry. I really am.
不管怎样, 我只是想让你知道我很抱歉 我真的很抱歉
Thank you.
谢谢
And though it came from an unexpected source,
尽管来自一个意料之外的人之口
Susan finally got the apology she'd always wanted.
Susan终于得到了她想要的道歉
Hey. Let me take those.
嗨, 我来拿那些东西
You're wearing a really big hat.
你戴着一顶非常大的帽子
Yes, I am.
是啊
Listen, the kids are watching a video,
听着, 孩子们正在看录像
which means that we've got only about 45 minutes until they actually find nemo,
就是说在他们找到现场转播之前 我们只有大概45分钟
so I suggest that we make the most of it.
我想我们应该尽可能地利用这段时间
By reliving your night out with the guys?
通过重新体验和你那些朋友的夜晚?
Lynette...
I'm trying.
我在努力
You look... ridiculous in that thing.
你戴着那个帽子看上去很可笑
Sexy ridiculous?
性感的可笑?
Maybe.
也许吧
I can live...
我接受这个...
with maybe.
也许
You know, it's going to take more than just this one night.
你要知道 这问题可不是你这样一晚就能解决的
I know.
我知道
Ah.
啊哈
Looks like we have an audience.
看起来我们有观众了
Let 'em look.
让他们看吧
As long as they don't try and cut in.
只要他们不试着介入
Dr. Goldfine.
Goldfine医生
Bree. We're not scheduled now, are we?
Bree, 我们没有预约现在见面吧?
I didn't have time to make an appointment.
我没有时间做预约
Rex moved out today.
Rex今天搬出去了
Oh, I'm very sorry to hear that,
哦, 真抱歉听到这个坏消息
but unfortunately, I'm completely booked right now.
但是不巧的是, 我现在的预约已经满了
I don't need much time.
我不会占用你很多时间
It just seems that you have more insight into my situation
只是你对于我的情况似乎比我自己
than I do, and I just think --
知道的更多, 我只是想...
Bree, we can't talk now.
Bree, 我们现在不能谈这个
If you could just tell me what he told you, then I could fix the problem.
如果你能告诉我他所告诉你的事情 我就能解决这问题了
I can't do that. It's completely unethical.
我不能那样做, 那完全违反职业道德
Well, why can't you
你为什么不能
-
that's my next appointment.
我的下一个预约者来了
You really need to go.
你必须离开
Dr. Goldfine, please.
Goldfine医生, 求求你了
Hold on. I'll go and talk to my client.
等一下, 我去和我的客户谈一下
Bree searched for Rex's audiotape hoping to find answers.
Bree搜寻了Rex的录音带 希望能够找到原因
She found answers, all right,
她的确找到了原因
but to entirely different questions.
但却是另外完全不同的问题的原因
I understand completely.
我完全理解
I'll
我
- I'll be out in just a minute.
- 我马上就好
Bree, I'm -- I'm sorry. He can't wait,
Bree, 对不起, 他不能等
but I can see you first thing in the morning -- 8:00.
但我可以在明早8点第一时间见你
8:00.
8点
Sorry to interupt.
抱歉打搅你了
Bye.
再见
Yes, I remember the world
是的, 我记得这世界
-every detail.
- 每一个细节
And what I remember most is how afraid I was.
而我印象最深的是我当时那么地害怕
What a waste.
真是浪费
You see, to live in fear is not to live at all.
你看, 恐惧中的生活根本不能算是生活
I wish I could tell this to those I left behind,
我希望我能把这个告诉我“身后”的那些人
but would it do any good?
但那会有用吗?
Probably not.
很可能不会
I understand now
我现在明白了
-
there will always be those who face their fears...
总有一些人敢于面对他们的恐惧...
and there will always be those who run away.
而总有一些人会选择逃避